Then, would you like to try going out?
Yeah, right. I'm sure...
No, my bad. Just kidding.
...is probably what he's
going to say to brush me off.
For real?
Huh? That's sort of not...
the reaction I was expecting.
I mean, how far do
you want to take this?
How... far?
Well, y'know... like holding hands,
hugging, having sex...
Se—?!
Se— Sexual activities are
out of the question!
She rephrased it...
Then how far? Kissing? Holding hands?
W-Well... that's...
'Cause if we don't do anything,
the "experiment" doesn't mean much, right?
Y-You have a point.
Huh? Does that mean I...
suggested something
I'm not ready for?
Hold on! Please let me
think about it for a bit!
Who gets that red from
the word "sex" these days?
Wh-What should I do?!
Wha?!
Just how in the world could
something like that happen?!
Please don't say it!
I'm well aware that I'm the
one who's acting strange.
I just... I really thought
he was just kidding, so...
I'm sure I was just feeling frustrated.
It always seems like I end up playing
into his hands before I realize it...
So I wanted to see how he'd react.
Even if just for a moment,
to see him flustered for once...
Why did I agree to it
before thinking it through?!
I never imagined...
that I'd actually end up dating him.
Oh?
Yoi-chan, you seemed
kinda girly just now.
I am a girl!
Now, now. What's wrong with
just casually dating him?
Yep, yep. It must have been meant to be.
There's so much talk about
"meant to be" and "fate" lately, but...
No way, seriously?
Why?!
What's going on?
I'm getting a bad feeling.
Oh?
Hey, Yoi Takiguichi-san!
I knew it!
And now there's more of them!
What, Takiguichi-san again?
Do you think something's up?
Enough!
I wonder what they're gonna talk about!
Right? I'm so curious.
I've had quite enough!
Could you please stop
coming to my classroom?
The other girls are staring at me.
And it seems there's more of you now.
'Sup, I'm Sentaro Akane.
I'm Shun Kuwabatake.
And...
Nobara and Kotobuki,
why are you guys here?
Huh?! Well, it seemed like you
guys were having fun, so…
Just getting the tea.
Are you Yoi-chan's friends?
I-I'm Kotobuki Hibiya.
I'm Nobara Tone.
Wh-Wh-What?
Okay!
I got you guys memorized now.
Fubuki-chan and Sumire-chan, right?
Not even close!
So, what happened to you thinking
things over about us dating?
What? What's this about, for real?!
Yes, thank you for that one!
Makes my heart flutter when he's direct!
You guys are gonna go out?!
Could you all please keep it down?
Regarding that matter, I gave it
some thought overnight.
Contract
Kohaku Ichimura (who will be referred to as "KI") and Yoi Takiguichi (who will be referred to as "YT")
would hereby adhere to the following conditions and agreement.
One, KI and YT shall establish a romantic relationship on an experimental basis for approximately two weeks to a month.
Contract
Kohaku Ichimura (who will be referred to as "KI") and Yoi Takiguichi (who will be referred to as "YT")
would hereby adhere to the following conditions and agreement.
One, KI and YT shall establish a romantic relationship on an experimental basis for approximately two weeks to a month.
Contract
Kohaku Ichimura (who will be referred to as "KI") and Yoi Takiguichi (who will be referred to as "YT")
would hereby adhere to the following conditions and agreement.
One, KI and YT shall establish a romantic relationship on an experimental basis for approximately two weeks to a month.
Contract
Kohaku Ichimura (who will be referred to as "KI") and Yoi Takiguichi (who will be referred to as "YT")
would hereby adhere to the following conditions and agreement.
One, KI and YT shall establish a romantic relationship on an experimental basis for approximately two weeks to a month.
Kohaku Ichimura, who will
be referred to as "KI,"
and Yoi Takiguichi, who will
be referred to as "YT,"
would hereby adhere to the following
conditions and agreement.
One, KI and YT shall establish
a romantic relationship on an
experimental basis for approximately
two weeks to a month.
One, KI and YT shall establish
a romantic relationship
on an experimental basis for
approximately two weeks to a month.
Two, KI and YT must keep
their romantic relationship
concealed and not disclose it
to any third party.
Two, KI and YT must keep their
romantic relationship concealed
and not disclose it to any third party.
Three, KI shall not engage in
any physical contact with YT,
including hugging, kissing,
and/or any sexual conduct.
Three, KI shall not engage in
any physical contact with YT,
including hugging, kissing,
and/or any sexual conduct.
However, this will not apply
to unintentional contact,
Huh? Is the Prince always like this?
such as accidentally
touching someone's hand.
Yeah, pretty much.
Furthermore, if either KI or YT
develops romantic feelings
for a separate third party,
either may immediately
terminate this contract.
That is all.
Oh, is that it?
You said you were gonna think it over,
so I'd figured you would just call it off.
Honestly, I considered that, too.
But I hate to give up on something
without seeing it through.
Okay!
After all that,
I'm allowed to date a prince.
Starting out normal would be no fun.
I shall do my best not to get
cut off during the cooling-off period.
The same. I look forward to it as well.
What, is a battle about to start?
Oh, that's the bell.
Yoi-chan, let's go.
Oh, right.
I have something I need to
discuss with Yoi-chan, so...
Huh?
Oh, I see.
Then let us leave the young ones to it.
H-Hey, wai—
What do you want to talk about?
Nah, I got nothing.
What?! Then why did you keep me behind?
Because I wanted some alone time with you.
Listen here!
But you're mine now, right?
I can keep you all to myself, can't I?
N-No, this is precisely what I mentioned
in the contract a second ago...
Huh?
Isn't this platonic contact?
I have to say, you seem
incredibly possessive, Senpai.
It's a bit far from your image,
don't you think?
Possessive?
That's a first.
Oh...
Actually, this might be the first time
I've ever really wanted something.
Huh? What... do you mean by that?
I actually forgot what I said.
Oh, this guy...
Just in case, could you please
give me your contact information?
Yeah, okay.
Are you a suspect?
The setup is a pain, don't ya think?
Huh?! Th-The bell!
Well, if you'll excuse me.
Oh, hey.
How about today?
Wanna walk home together?
N-No... It'd be bad if word got out.
Oh, all right.
Okay, if anything comes up let me know.
Wanna walk home together?
Wow. Words like that just
roll off his tongue, huh?
While I'm flustered just
at the thought of dating a man...
I mean... he'd be my very first
boyfriend, right?
Technically...
Yoi-chan! Yoi-chan! Yoi-chan!
Am I okay? Did I really make
the right choice choosing him?
Am I gradually becoming
numb to all this?!
Actually, this might be the first time
I've ever really wanted something.
Gyoza for two coming right up!
Yay! Want some?
Nah...
What's up?
Is it your mom again?
Aw, gross!
What? What's going on?
My bad. Just got taken by surprise.
I-I sent it.
Good evening.
This is my first time messaging.
It's Takiguichi.
After thinking a little on what we
spoke about today, I would like to
propose the following:
How about a date next Saturday
or Sunday?
Things like "meant to be"
or "fate" or "Prince"...
You have to determine
those things for yourself.
Is she for real?
What? Look at that!
Handsome, right?
Man, what a hottie!
That guy's hot, huh?
But they're wearing a skirt,
so they might be a girl!
Maybe arriving thirty minutes
early was a bit much...
Wow! She's really hot, then!
I mean, it was okay to ask him out, right?
Was I too eager?
But this is really the only
way to see if we're compatible...
The one thing that bothers me is that...
Got it.
His reply was unexpectedly dismissive.
I thought he'd be more forward.
Yoi-chan.
Yo.
H-Hello.
I'm just starting to
get super nervous now.
Seriously though, you're here
way ahead of schedule.
I had a feeling you might be,
so I'm glad I got here early.
He read my mind.
Also, why are you in your uniform?
I-I had something to do at
school before coming here...
Uh-huh.
Or not...
I can't admit that I was
agonizing over what to wear
before finally defaulting to
my school uniform.
You have some place you wanna hit today?
Huh? No, I just figured we'd be
going to the movies or something.
How about you, Senpai?
Me? I've got no plans.
Then, why don't we go look at clothes?
What? No, I'm not really into...
Honestly, I really want to
see you in all kinds of clothes.
To the movies, then.
Grab
H-Hey, um, the movies...
Don't worry, don't worry!
Y-You look wonderful!
Thank you very much.
This wasn't the kind of store I expected.
Wow! That looks great on you!
Huh? Yoi-chan?!
Seriously?! It looks real good on you!
Thanks.
Hey, face this way a little.
It's so weird... Why can't
I look Senpai in the face?
And anyway, why are you
getting dressed, too?!
Hmm? Oh, you mean this?
I was thinking I'd match your style.
I don't get it.
I mean, see?
Don't we look good together like this?
Oh... The shoulder, sorry about that.
What was that?
Normally, girls try on cuter clothes,
and if you're going to match,
it'd be matching couple clothes.
But right now, my clothes don't look
like what you'd wear on a date.
Darn it... I don't know why, but the
shoulder he touched feels so tense.
And... you're just gonna go back
to what you were wearing, huh?
The sticker shock was too much for me.
Are you sure you're okay not buying it?
Yes! I don't need it!
Spoiled rich kids are just so...
Brown Sugar
Warabi Mochi
What? A Japanese confectionery?
Yoi-chan, you like sweet things?
No, not particularly.
Well, why not? I was starting
to get a bit hungry anyway.
Apricot
Jam
Bean Daifuku
Lemon Daifuku
Moon Viewing
Rabbit Manju
I want the mitarashi dango.
How about you, Yoi-chan?
Hmm... What should I choose...
Well, shall we eat?
Sounds good.
Man, that's good.
I know, right?
The red bean paste in the
daifuku is the smooth kind!
So good!
Huh? Is there really a difference
between the clumpy and smooth?
There sure is! They're totally different!
The clumpy kind isn't bad, but
when you eat mochi and such,
don't you feel a bit let down
when it's not the smooth kind?!
No, it's never crossed my mind.
Oh, it's completely out of the question!
The texture and mouthfeel
are completely different.
Man, you really like
sweet things, don't you?
N-No more than most people.
Then what's your favorite snack?
Choco anpan, oreos, and
Alfort chocolate cookies.
What do you put on your toast?
Butter and condensed milk.
You've got a serious sweet tooth!
Do... Do I?
Not even aware of it, are ya?
Whoa...
The corners of his mouth
lift up so beautifully.
When he smiles, he looks so kind.
Like a completely different person.
I feel like... I really learned something
about Senpai for the first time.
We can probably do one more place.
Hmm... Yeah, you're right.
Flower Garden
An amusement park?
But it's almost closing time, you know.
Yeah. We won't stay long.
Wasn't... expecting that.
Okay then, off you go!
Y'know,
I really like amusement parks at
night just before they close.
It's beautiful, but vaguely melancholic.
I like fireworks in the winter, too.
Oh, I know that feeling.
Ice cream tastes better
in the winter, too.
See? I knew you liked sweet stuff.
Well, that's not...
We often know ourselves the least.
Today, he's less "Senpai" and more
"Kohaku Ichimura"...
Do you always...
go on dates like these?
Oh. No, this is a first.
I usually just go wherever
the other person wants to go
and go along with their vibe.
I don't have any desire
to any particular thing with anyone.
Even the clothing store was a first for me.
What, really?
I assumed you knew about
that sort of stuff.
Not at all.
I'm always just wearing whatever
an acquaintance gives me.
What kind of acquaintance is that?
But...
Today was super fun.
Thank you.
Senpai's profile, illuminated
from the lights, was so beautiful...
I couldn't take my eyes off of him.
From the way you messaged me,
I thought I was bothering you.
What? I sent you a reply, didn't I?
It felt incredibly dismissive.
I... usually leave messages
like that on read, but...
I wanted to reply to yours immediately...
even if it wasn't much.
Got it.
O-Oh, I... see.
Yeah.
Welcome back!
All right, I'll open the door now.
Well then... Let's head home.
Okay.
Are we really going home already?
I wanted to reply to yours immediately...
Going home right now
seems like a waste...
Hey.
Wanna grab something to eat?
Huh, oh, yes!
Okay, what're ya feeling?
Uh, I can't think of anything
when you ask me like that...
I'm serious, it's right there!
There's a super delicious gyoza place!
Since the gyoza king has spoken,
I guess we'll give it a try.
Gyoza sounds good.
Let's follow them.
Yeah.
Seriously, it's pretty badass,
ending a first date with gyoza.
Oh, just a moment.
Um, I'm sorry.
They're short-staffed at work,
and asked me to come in.
Oh, yeah?
I'm sorry!
It's fine, it's fine. No prob.
Then let's call it a night.
I really... wanted to eat gyoza.
Nasu Oyaji Curry
Thank you so much for
going out of your way.
Nah, thank you.
You're the one who invited me.
Later.
Um!
If you'd like...
you can eat at our place?
Ah!
Yoi, you're finally here!
Ugh! Dad!
Huh? Aren't you the one
from the other day?
Oh, hello.
Huh? What's this?
Are you two actually going out?!
D-Dad!
Oh, yeah, we actually are.
What, no way!
Then he's your first boyfriend?!
Congratulations, Yoi!
Forget it!
Hey, hey, hey! What about
Yoi made you like her?!
Come on! Hurry up and get back to work!
Um, well...
Come on, your dad wants to know!
In all honesty, her looks?
Y'know, if I go out with her,
I can look at her all day.
So I guess I wanted the right to do that.
Well, that just about covers it.
What a unique kid.
Let's go, Dad.
Huh? But I still haven't
introduced myself...
You don't need to do that!
Oh, is that so...
Well, goodbye.
You're laughing too much.
Sorry, sorry!
C'mon, the right to look at her all day!
The Prince is such a stalker.
No, it's just downright scary!
Green Tea
I was having so much fun,
and it was ruined in an instant!
What?!
Wh-What?
Yoi just said she had
"fun" with the Prince!
Yep, yep.
Well, no, this is just...
It's really not like that, it's just...
But... it really was fun.
Oh my, oh my!
Just make it official already!
N-No, I mean... Yes, it was fun,
but we still don't know if
that's love or not, right?
Well, that just about covers it.
That's right...
Before considering what's
"fate" and "meant to be,"
I don't know if this is even "love."
Hang in there.
You're always making the Prince
angry, aren't you, Ichi?
Ugh, I hate chemistry.
Today might be a rough one.
Right?
You know, chemistry is human wisdom.
Where did that come from?
Yo.
Y-You scared me! What...?
Why don't you just approach
me the normal way?!
You're the one who said not to come
to your classroom anymore.
Also, why are you ignoring me?
Did I upset you again somehow?
B-Because... You told my dad
all about us dating, and...
What? We weren't at school, so it
doesn't have to be a secret, does it?
B-But...
there's a chance that we
might not be dating, don't you think?
Wha... There is? Why?
Wh-What do you mean, why?
When it comes to love,
you can't get into a relationship
unless at least one
person likes the other.
But all you say is,
"I want to watch you forever"
or, "Show me what kind of face
you'll make next" and...
Is that actually "love?"
Unawareness
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Yukari Murase-Louden
Andy Ellis
Gabriella Alabanza
Salem Alabanza
Elizabeth Ellis